Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Motion Pictures
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Videorecordings documenting Yale University, 1966-2008; Accession 2009-A-156
  - 3364: Kelly Brownell - Fat Tax, 1997 June 27; 1 (Box 272)
  - 3396: Child Discipline, 1997 June 29; 1 (Box 297)
  - 3422: Graduate Tuition, 1997 July 16; 1 (Box 313)
  - 3172: Yale China: Impressions of exchange students, Chinese high school students tour ofAmerican colleges, 1997 July 30; 1 (Box 955)
  - 3367: Trout Fisherman, 1997 August 3; 1 (Box 274)
  - 3368: Wendell Bell - Futurology, 1997 August 10; 1 (Box 275)
  - 3662: Potential for Doing Harm, 1997 August 10; 1 (Box 438)
  - 3376: Orthodox Jewish Student Debate, 1997 September 11; 1 (Box 282)
  - 3684: The Yale Egg, 1997 October 1; 1 (Box 457)
  - 3517: Media Training Tape 1, 1997 December 10; 1 (Box 367)
  - 3518: Media Training Tape 2, 1997 December 10; 1 (Box 369)
  - 3402: Yale Financial Aid, 1998 February 1; 1 (Box 302)
  - 3685: Richard Laven on CNN, 1998 February 5; 1; Very poor quality video recording on the tape; unable to improve the quality during digitization. (Box 458)
  - 3372: Nixson Documentary, 1998 February 20; 1 (Box 278)
  - 3384: Architecture at Yale University, 1998 February 20; 1 (Box 286)
  - 3369: Reinventing Yale, 1998 February 26; 1 (Box 276)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 276U)
  - 3535: Dean Richard Wood discusses President Clinton, 1998 April 2; 1 (Box 135)
  - 3382: Yale Class Day, 1998 May 24; 1 (Box 931)
  - 3680: Yale University's Graduation Ceremonies, 1998 May 24-29; 1 (Box 454)
  - 3427: Yale Reunion, 1998 May 29; 1 (Box 318)
  - 3562: Maboroshi no Daitouryou Shinbun, 1998 August 1; 1 (Box 403)
  - 3385: E. Coli Special, 1998 August 5; 1 (Box 287)
  - 3383: Sen. Dodd, Genetic Testing Lab, live event, 1998 August 11; 1 (Box 873)
  - 3381: Sen. Dodd, Genetic Testing Lab, news clips, 1998 August 21; 1 (Box 285)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 285U)
  - 3426: Freshman Speech, 1998 August 29; 1 (Box 317)
  - 3659: Mind Bugs, 1998 August 30; 1 (Box 435)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 435U)
  - 3287: Yale's Altman Wins Nobel Prize, 1998 October 1; 1 (Box 195)
  - 3425: Racial Prejudice, 1998 October 10; 1 (Box 316)
  - Renewal and Renaissance, Building Yale for the 21st: Yale renovations
    - 3437: Kimmel and Winney interviews, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 325)
    - 3438: Beckett and student interviews, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 913)
    - 3439: Student interviews, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 878)
    - 3440: Swing Space and Music Library b-roll, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 879)
    - 3441: Opening of the Music Library, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 880)
    - 3443: Old Campus, Berkeley b-roll, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 881)
    - 3444: Crilley and Brodhead interviews, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 882)
    - 3445: Brodhead and Levin interviews, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 883)
    - 3447: Peterson and student interviews, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 884)
    - 3448: Swing Space and Payne Whitney b-roll, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 885)
    - 3449: Payne Whitney b-roll, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 886)
    - 3450: Crane shots of Sterling, Payne Whitney, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 887)
    - 3452: Crane shots of Music School, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 888)
    - 3458: Highlights and interviews, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 877)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 877U)
  - 3454: Yale Bump #2, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 326)
  - 3455: Yale Bump, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 327)
  - 3456: Yale Bump - music, 1998 October 19; 1 (Box 328)
  - 3380: Divinity School, 1998 November 5; 1 (Box 284)
  - 3563: In the Still of the Night, 1998 November 15; 1 (Box 404)
  - 3007: Renewal and Renaissance Building Yale for the 21st, 1998 November 10; 1 (Box 4)
  - 3379: New Wrinkle Remover, 1998 November 18; 1 (Box 283)
  - 4279: A Town Torn Apart, documentary, 1998 November 30; 1 (Box 864)
  - 3469: Yale / Harvard football, 1999; 1 (Box 333)
  - 3473: Freshman Orientation: Introduction to student life for freshmen; 1999 reunion archive, 1 (Box 940)
  - 3658: Balloon Angioplasty, 1999; 1 (Box 434)
  - 3670: Levin Baccalaureate, 1999; 1 (Box 445)
  - 3903: Yale Harvard Football Game, taped from DirecTV, 1999; 1 (Box 555)
  - 3908: HKUST Court Video, 1999; 1 (Box 560)
  - 4210: Vox Et Musica for Yale Reunions, 1999; 1 (Box 812)
  - 3500: AYA Vox Musica 1999, 1999 January 1; 1 (Box 349)
  - 3515: 1999 Leadership Award from Chamber of Commerce for NH, 1999 January 1; 1 (Box 365)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 365U)
  - 3543: Designing Minds: Arts in Education, 1999 January 1; 1 (Box 385)
  - 3556: Tuition Costs, 1999 January 1; 1 (Box 397)
  - 3392: Burial of Edward Bouchet, 1999 January 18; 1 (Box 293)
  - 3674: Jovin Murder, WVIT-TV, 1999 January 20; 1 (Box 449)
  - 3665: Jovin Murder, 1999 February 1, March 12; 1 (Box 441)
  - 3430: Yale Research Building Opening, 1999 February 10; 1 (Box 321)
  - 3243: Hate Crimes, 1999 February 19; 1 (Box 156)
  - 3238: Robert Stern and Phillip Johnson, PBS and CBS, 1999 February 24; 1 (Box 151)
  - 3922: Tonight Show, 1999 March 17; 1 (Box 571)
  - 3767: Pioneers and Competitors, 1999 April 1; 1 (Box 473)
  - 3471: Yale Bumps b-roll, students moving in, New Haven life, 1999 April 8; 1 (Box 938)
  - 3472: Reunion 1999, select reel campus, only audio, 1999 April 8; 1 (Box 939)
  - 4171: WTNH-TV New Haven,WVIT-TV Hartford, 1999 April 9-16; 1 (Box 784)
  - 3421: David Gergen Speech, Yale Class Day, 1999 May 23; 1 (Box 937)
  - 3664: Fertility Reel, 1999 June 1; 1 (Box 440)
  - 3538: News coverage of Don Brown's strategy game "Octi", 1999 June 11; 1 (Box 380)
  - 3428: Maple Cottage, 1999 July 7; 1 (Box 319)
  - 3516: David Gergin - Ben Carson Dialogue, 1999 September 7; 1 (Box 366)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 366U)
  - 3666: Vision Exhibit, 1999 September 7; 1 (Box 442)
  - 4165: National Eye Institute "Vision Exhibit", 1999 September 7; 1 (Box 778)
  - 3574: Chamber of Commerce Award for President Levin, 1999 October 1; 1 (Box 415)
  - 3575: Procter and Gamble Company History: Yale Segment, John Pepper Retirement, Bright Light Productions, 1999 October 19; 1 (Box 416)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 416U)
  - 4296: Cutways (Window Dub), Greater New Haven Chamber of Commerce, 1999 October 21; 1 (Box 408)
  - 4297: R. Levin Raw #2 (Window Dub), 1999 October 21; 1 (Box 414)
  - 3519: The Times Capsule Hour 1, 1999 December 7; 1 (Box 370)
  - 3520: The Times Capsule Hour 2, 1999 December 7; 1 (Box 371)
  - 3955: Jovin Murder, WTNH, 1999 December 8; 1 (Box 596)
  - 3099: Communiversity Day 2000 tape 1, 1 (Box 59)
  - 3100: Communiversity Day 2000 tape 2, 1 (Box 60)
  - 3212: News Channel 8 Tercentennial features, 2000 January 1; 1 (Box 130)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 130U)
  - 3780: Lehrer News Hour, Dr. Gelernter, 2000 January 5; 1 (Box 483)
  - 3770: Living the Dream, 2000 January 17; 1 (Box 476)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 476U)
  - 3782: Science Hill Clips, WTNH, 2000 January 20; 1 (Box 485)
  - 3783: Science Hill Clips, WVIT and WTIC, 2000 January 20; 1 (Box 907)
  - 3784: Science Hill clips, WFSB and CNN, 2000 January 20; 1 (Box 906)
  - 3787: Burden of Proof, 2000 January 25; 1 (Box 488)
  - 3778: Patch From Yale, 2000 February 16; 1 (Box 481)
  - 3795: Jovin Murder, 2000 February 29; 1 (Box 495)
  - 3817: Yale Garments, 2000 February 29; 1 (Box 512)
  - 3777: Racial Bias Testing, Dateline, 2000 March 19; 1 (Box 480)
  - 3952: New Cops on the Block, NHPD documentary, 2000 March 24; 1 (Box 593)
  - 3996: On Broadway, 2000 April 1; 1 (Box 631)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 631U)
  - 3785: Lehrer News Hour, 2000 April 5; 1 (Box 486)
  - 3588: Warner and Co. Yale Video Catalog 101, 2000 April 17; 1 (Box 418)
  - 3589: Warner and Co. Yale Video Catalog 102, 2000 April 17; 1 (Box 419)
  - 3101: Pow Wow 2000 Tape 1, 2000 April 23; 1 (Box 61)
  - 3102: Pow Wow 2000 Tape 2, 2000 April 23; 1 (Box 62)
  - 3189: Alley Cats performance, 2000 April 25; 1 (Box 11)
  - 3222: Celebrate Yale 300 Alumni interviews, 2000 June 2; 1 (Box 139)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 139U)
  - 3240: Yale Campaign School for Women, WVIT, 2000 June 16; 1 (Box 153)
  - 3241: Peter the Great, 2000 June 28; 1 (Box 154)
  - 3781: Genaissance, 2000 August 3; 1 (Box 484)
  - 3675: Yale 300 Preview, 2000 August 19; 1 (Box 450)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 450U)
  - 4091: Yale 300th Preview, Channel 8 News, 2000 August 19; 1 (Box 728)
  - 3998: Orientation Video, 2000 August 28; 1 (Box 632)
  - 3218: Student Move in Day, 2000 September 1; 1 (Box 136)
  - 3773: Sally Hemings: Redefining History, 2000 September 21; 1 (Box 478)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 478U)
  - 4228: Tercentennial Features, WTNH-Ch. 8, 2000 October - 2001 September; 1 (Box 829)
  - 3868: Gilmore Girls, Pilot, 2000 October 5; 1 (Box 537)
  - 3175: News coverage of tercentennial, 2000 October 13; 1 (Box 100)
  - 3176: Yale's 300th Anniversary, 2000 October 13; 1 (Box 101)
  - 3177: Yale's 300th Anniversary, 2000 October 15; 1 (Box 102)
  - 3178: Yale's 300th Anniversary, 2000 October 16; 1 (Box 103)
  - 3179: Tercentennial news coverage, WVIT, 2000 October 19; 1 (Box 104)
  - 3180: Tercentennial news coverage, WTNH, 2000 October 19; 1 (Box 868)
  - 3185: Skakel hearing news coverage, WFSB, 2000 October 20; 1 (Box 109)
  - 3186: Skakel hearing news coverage, WTNH, 2000 October 20; 1 (Box 95)
  - 3561: Opening of new Yale Boathouse, 2000 October 20; 1 (Box 402)
  - 3693: WVIT News Friday, 2000 October 20; 1 (Box 466)
  - 3049: Yale Tercentenial Open house, 2000 October 21; 1 (Box 22)
  - 3187: Tercentennial news coverage, WFSB, 2000 October 21; 1 (Box 110)
  - 3188: Tercentennial news coverage, WVIT, 2000 October 21; 1 (Box 869)
  - 3191: Yale's 300th Anniversary, 2000 October 21; 1 (Box 113)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 113U)
  - 3194: News Channel 8 Tercentennial coverage, 2000 October 21; 1 (Box 115)
  - 3195: CT news coverage of tercentennial, union rally, 2000 October 21; 1 (Box 116)
  - 3683: Michigan v. Michigan State Football Game, 2000 October 21; 1 (Box 456)
  - 3193: Yale's 300th Anniversary, 2000 October 22; 1 (Box 114)
  - 3565: Special on Asperner syndrome, 2000 October 26; 1 (Box 406)
  - 3054: Aaron Copland Concert, 2000 November 8; 1 (Box 25)
  - 3051: Yale Stage Blue tape 1, 2000 November 13; 1 (Box 23)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 23U)
  - 3052: Yale Stage Blue tape 2, 2000 November 13; 1 (Box 24)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 24U)
  - 3228: Interview with Vincent Scully, 2000 November 21; 1 (Box 144)
  - 3203: Yale 300: Behind the Ivy, WTNH, 2000 December 14; 1 (Box 124)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 124U)
  - 3477: Yale 300: Behind the Ivy, 2000 December 14; 1 (Box 894)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 894U)
  - 3884: Yale 300: Behind the Ivy: Looking Back at Yale, WTNH, 2000 December 14; 1 (Box 914)
  - 3087: Flying Yale logo, 2000 December 20; 1 (Box 49)
  - 3870: Gilmore Girls, Rory's Dance, 2000 December 20; 1 (Box 539)
  - 3000: Adventures of SuperLinda, Tercentennial, 2001; 1 (Box 1)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 1U)
  - 3001: Bowl show, 2001; 1 (Box 2)
  - 3009: 300 Years A Tercentennial Tribute, 2001; 1 (Box 6)
  - 3088: Yale 300 lower 3rd, 2001; 1 (Box 50)
  - 3115: Yale 300 logos, 2001; 1 (Box 73)
  - 3117: Celebrate Yale 300 w/birthday greetings, 2001; 1 (Box 75)
  - 3128: Yale Admissions Video, 2001; 1 (Box 86)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 86U)
  - 3476: 300 Years: A Tercentennial Tribute, 2001; 1 (Box 337)
  - 3482: Opening Yale 300, highlights of tercentennial events with alternate ending, 1905 June 23; 1 (Box 338)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 338U)
  - 3534: Yale Promo tape and Opening Yale 300, 2001; 1 (Box 377b)
  - 3527: Yale Promo tape and Opening Yale 300 [PAL format], 2001; 1 (Box 377a)
  - 3555: Straight to the Heart - The Life of Henri Nouwen, 2001; 1 (Box 396)
  - 3557: Y300 Final Review, 2001; 1 (Box 398)
  - 3560: Yale at 300, summary of PBS and BBC documentaries, 2001; 1 (Box 401)
  - 3894: Yale B-roll, 2001; 1 (Box 965)
  - 4084: Opening Yale 300, 2001; 1 (Box 707)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 707U)
  - 4085: Yale 300th Channel 8 News, 2001; 1 (Box 708)
  - 4086: Yale's Tercentennial in China, 2001; 1 (Box 709)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 709U)
  - 4092: CPT/PBS Yale at 300, 2001; 1 (Box 715)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 715U)
  - 4093: Yale 300th Anniversary News Montage, 2001; 1 (Box 716)
  - 4097: Celebrate Yale 300, 2001; 1 (Box 720)
  - 4099: Paul Kennedy A and I/Tercentennial, 2001; 1 (Box 722)
  - 4103: Tercentennial, 2001; 1 (Box 725)
  - 4140: Yale University Democratic Vistas, William Clyde DeVane Lectures
    - Kronman, Anthony T., "The Democratic Soul," tape 1, 2001; 1 (Box 756)
    - Bromwich, David, "Abraham Lincoln and Walt Whitman," tape 2, 2001; 1 (Box 757)
    - Banaji, Mahrazin R., "Ordinary Prejudice," tape 3, 2001; 1 (Box 758)
    - Shapiro, Ian, "Democracy and Distribution," tape 4, 2001; 1 (Box 759)
    - Denning, Michael, "The Democracy as Social Movement," tape 6, 2001; 1 (Box 760)
    - Ackerman, Bruce, "The Death of Citizenship?," tape 7, 2001; 1 (Box 761)
    - Steitz, Joan A., "Origins of the Biomedical Revolution," tape 8, 2001; 1 (Box 762)
    - Gelernter, David, "Democracy and Computers," tape 9, 2001; 1 (Box 763)
    - Brodhead, Richard, "Taking Democracy to School," tape 10, 2001; 1 (Box 764)
    - Cott, Nancy E., "Democracy and the Family," tape 11, 2001; 1 (Box 765)
    - Carter, Stephen L., "Can Religion Tolerate Democracy?," tape 12, 2001; 1 (Box 766)
    - Gaddis, John L., "Democracy and Foreign Policy," tape 13, 2001; 1 (Box 767)
    - Scott, James C., "Meritocracy and Democracy," tape 14, 2001; 1 (Box 768)
  - 4164: Celebrate Yale 300, 2001; 1 (Box 777)
  - 4215: WTNH Ch. 8: News Features, 2001 January-March; 1 (Box 816)
  - 3214: News Channel 8 Tercentennial features, 2001 January 1; 1 (Box 870)
  - 3224: Student interviews, 2001 January 1; 1 (Box 141)
  - 3506: Democratic Soul, 2001 January 9; 1 (Box 356)
  - 3508: Lincoln and Whitman as Representative Americans, 2001 January 16; 1 (Box 358)
  - 3509: Paradoxes of the Mind and Society, 2001 January 23; 1 (Box 359)
  - 3539: Democratic Vistas: Democracy and Distribution, 2001 January 30; 1 (Box 381)
  - 3791: Bruce Alexander, CT business with Joe Perna, 2001 February 1; 1 (Box 492)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 492U)
  - 3223: Drama School interviews, 2001 February 7; 1 (Box 140)
  - 3507: The Democracy as a Social Movement, 2001 February 13; 1 (Box 357)
  - 3566: The Death of Citizenship?, 2001 February 20; 1 (Box 407)
  - 3510: American Democracy and the Origins of the Biomedical Revolution, 2001 February 27; 1 (Box 360)
  - 3093: Yale Repertory Theatre, 2001 March 3; 1 (Box 53)
  - 3503: Democracy and Computer - Pitfalls, Possibilities, 2001 March 20; 1 (Box 353)
  - 3505: Democracy and Education, 2001 March 20; 1 (Box 355)
  - 3026: Making a Difference, highlight, impact of Yale graduates, Channel 8, 2001 March 23; 1 (Box 943)
  - 3217: Yale 300: Making a Difference, 2001 March 23; 1 (Box 134)
  - 3810: Handsome Dan, 2001 March 24; 1 (Box 508)
  - 3808: Jovin Murder, WTNH, 2001 March 27; 1 (Box 507)
  - 3809: Jovin Murder, WVIT and WTIC, 2001 March 27; 1 (Box 911)
  - 3809: Jovin Murder, WFSB-CBS, 2001 March 27; 1 (Box 730)
  - 3038: Promo, Tercentennial logo loop, 2001 March 29; 1 (Box 814)
  - 3999: Andrea Pizziconi, 2001 March 29; 1 (Box 633)
  - 3211: Yale 300: Facing the Future, WTNH Channel 8 coverage of 2001 tercentennial graduation ceremonies, 2001 March 30; 1 (Box 928)
  - 3199: Clinton's tercentennial speech, 2001 April 1; 1 (Box 120)
  - 3947: Sidra Bell Dancers, WTNH, 2001 April 1; 1 (Box 591)
  - 4107: Tercentennial: Levin/Bush/Kennedy, 2001 April 1; 1 (Box 732)
  - 3502: Democracy and Family, 2001 April 3; 1 (Box 352)
  - 3227: Interview with Dean Blocker, 2001 April 5; 1 (Box 143)
  - 3215: Yale 300: Making a Difference, Channel 8 News, Yale's graduates and contributions to society, 2001 April 6; 1 (Box 929)
  - 3216: Yale 300: Making a Difference, Yale Graduates and Contributions to Society, Channel 8 News, 2001 April 6; 1 (Box 133)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 133U)
  - 3479: Yale 300: Making a Difference, 2001 April 6; 1 (Box 895)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 895U)
  - 3572: Yale 300: Making a Difference - short version, 2001 April 6; 1 (Box 413)
  - 3504: Democracy and Foreign Policy, 2001 April 10; 1 (Box 354)
  - 3542: CT Journal Compilation, David Budries, 2001 April 13; 1 (Box 384)
  - 4106: Inventing the Modern Game of Football, 2001 April 16; 1 (Box 731)
  - 3569: Democracy and Foreign Policy, 2001 April 17; 1 (Box 410)
  - 3044: Royal Blue Concert, 2001 April 19; 1 (Box 17)
  - 3027: Light Blue, people entering the show and the show, hand camera, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 944)
  - 3028: Light Blue, camera 1, people entering the show and the show, balcony camera, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 945)
  - 3029: Light Blue, camera 2, various shots, including Bush entrance, balcony camera, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 946)
  - 3030: Light Blue switched show, from various camra angles, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 947)
  - 3046: Yale Tercentennial B-roll tape 1, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 19)
  - 3047: Yale Tercentennial B-roll tape 2, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 20)
  - 3048: Yale Tercentennial B-roll tape 3, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 21)
  - 3076: Tercentennial Weekend Welcome, panel discussion with alumni Reuben and Yellen, economic advisors to President Clinton, live event, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 44)
  - 3077: Tercentennial Weekend Welcome audience b-roll, audience shots during panel discussion, live event, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 920)
  - 3196: Yale's 300th Anniversary, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 117)
  - 3889: Levin, Rubin, Yellen, afternoon at Woolsey Hall, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 942)
  - 3891: Light Blue, switched, 2001 April 20; 1 (Box 962)
  - Merson, Rosser, and Williams, "The Globalization of Health Services", 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 967)
  - 3045: Wayne reception tape 1, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 18)
  - 3055: Yale Tercentennial Dinner, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 26)
  - 3058: Democracy in America, live event, professors speak about democracy in America, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 850)
  - 3059: Globilization of Health Service, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 29)
  - 3060: Leading the way with Math tape 1, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 30)
  - 3061: Leading the way with Math tape 2, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 31)
  - 3062: Leading the way with Math tape 3, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 32)
  - 3063: Women, Gender and Sexuality, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 33)
  - 3064: Yale Law School and the Law of Sexual Harrassment, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 34)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 34U)
  - 3065: Yale a leader in African studies tape 1, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 35)
  - 3066: Yale a leader in African studies tape 2, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 36)
  - 3067: Yale a leader in African studies tape 3, 2001 April 21 (Box 37)
  - 3068: World Famous for Song: Musical Performances by Cole Porter and Charles Ives, live event, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 851)
  - 3069: Yale Cancer Center: Opening the Black Box, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 38)
  - 3070: Kurt Weill's "Down in the Valley," live event, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 853)
  - 3071: Robert Stern on Architecture at Yale tape 1, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 39)
  - 3072: Robert Stern on Architecture at Yale tape 2, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 40)
  - 3073: Robert Stern on Architecture at Yale tape 3, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 41)
  - 3074: Robert Stern on Architecture at Yale, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 42)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 42U)
  - 3075: Tom Wolfe: His Life at Yale, Tercentennial live event, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 43)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 43U)
  - 3103: News Clips tercentennial, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 63)
  - 3106: Tercentennial Dinner: Invocation, Music, and Speakers, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 953)
  - 3657: 300 Years of Creativity and Discovery, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 433)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 433U)
  - 3682: 300 Years of Creativity and Discovery, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 905)
  - 3890: Bush, 2001 April 21; 1 (Box 961)
  - 3937: Skull and Bones, 2001 April 23; 1 (Box 584)
  - 3511: Meritocracy and Democracy, 2001 April 24; 1 (Box 361)
  - 3163: Levin in China, Chinese language news coverage, 2001 May 1; 1 (Box 90)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 90U)
  - 3162: Levin in China, English language news, 2001 May 1; 1 (Box 91)
  - 3162: Levin in China, CCTV English language news, 2001 May 1; 1 (Box 92)
  - 3164: Levin's Visit in Beijing, 2001 May 1; 1 (Box 93)
  - 3165: Levin in China, English language news interview, 2001 May 1; 1 (Box 94)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 94U)
  - 3166: Levin in China, Chinese language CCTV coverage, 2001 May 1; 1 (Box 96)
  - 3171: Yale: 300 Years of Creativity and Discovery [PAL format], 2001 May 1; 1 (Box 99a)
  - 3170: Yale: 300 Years of Creativity and Discovery, videotape (PAL format), 2001 May 1; 1 (Box 99b)
  - 3568: Pictures for the People, 2001 May 1; 1 (Box 409)
  - 3169: Levin in China, CNN and CNBC coverage, 2001 May 2; 1 (Box 98)
  - 3167: Levin in China, CCTV English language news, 2001 May 7; 1 (Box 97)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 97U)
  - 3987: Yale Spot, WTNH, 2001 May 11; 1 (Box 622)
  - 3989: Jester, 2001 May 11; 1 (Box 624)
  - 3079: CSPAN Broadcast Yale and Public Service, 2001 May 12; 1 (Box 45)
  - 3790: George Bush, 2001 May 12; 1 (Box 491)
  - 3946: The Today Show, Dr. David Leffell, 2001 May 15; 1 (Box 590)
  - 3107: Yale Class Day with Hilary Clinton's Speech, 2001 May 20; 1 (Box 954)
  - 3108: Hillary Clinton, 2001 May 20; 1 (Box 66)
  - 3788: Yale Tercentennial, Sid Evans Production, 2001 May 20; 1 (Box 489)
  - 3109: Yale Commencement, 2001 May 21; 1 (Box 67)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 67U)
  - 3197: President Bush Gets Degree, 2001 May 21; 1 (Box 118)
  - 3078: President G. W. Bush speaking at commencement, 2001 May 26; 1 (Box 921)
  - 3225: Alumni interviews, 2001 May 27; 1 (Box 142)
  - 3475: Yale's Tercentennial in China, 2001 May 29; 1 (Box 336)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 336U)
  - 3129: Lindsay Davenport Pilot Pen Street Clinic, 2001 July 11; 1 (Box 87)
  - 3121: Yale Club of Southwest Florida, 2001 July 20; 1 (Box 79)
  - 3127: Yale College Wrexham [PAL format], 2001 August 5; 1 (Box 85A)
  - 3127: Yale College Wrexham, 2001 August 5; 1 (Box 85B)
  - 3125: Yale Club of New Haven, 2001 August 19; 1 (Box 83)
  - 3559: Iran's Dilemma: The Islamic Republic and the Current Middle East Crisis, 2001 August 29; 1 (Box 400)
  - 3131: Jack Ford, 2001 September 5; 1 (Box 88)
  - 3976: Yale AIDS Vaccine, Channel 30, 2001 September 6; 1 (Box 612)
  - 3095: Tercentennial B-roll tape 2, 2001 September 7; 1 (Box 55)
  - 3096: Tercentennial B-roll tape 3, 2001 September 7; 1 (Box 56)
  - 3219: Celebrate Yale 300, 2001 September 7; 1 (Box 137)
  - 3097: Levin Tercentennial gala interview, 2001 September 14; 1 (Box 57)
  - NESN Yale special
    - 3460: Interviews with captains of golf, track, swimming and gymnastics, 2001 September 20; 1 (Box 330)
    - 3461: Interviews with captains of squash, rowing, and tennis, 2001 September 20; 1 (Box 893)
    - 3462: Interviews with captains of baseball and basketball, 2001 September 20; 1 (Box 889)
    - 3465: Squash practice b-roll, 2001 September 20; 1 (Box 890)
    - 3466: Swimming and crew tanks b-roll, 2001 September 20; 1 (Box 891)
    - 3459: Football voiceover, 2001 September 24 (Box 329)
    - 3464: Student athletes, 2001 September 24; 1 (Box 331)
    - 3467: Yale hockey defeats Boston College, undated; 1 (Box 892)
  - 3939: Paul Bracken, 2001 September 25; 1 (Box 585)
  - 3468: NESN Yale special - Motion Control, 2001 September 28; 1 (Box 332)
  - 3816: Bill Clinton on Campus, 2001 October 1; 1 (Box 511)
  - 3912: Opening Yale 300, 2001 October 1; 1 (Box 562)
  - 4186: President Clinton - Tercentennial, 2001 October 1; 1 (Box 797)
  - 3558: Is Security Possible When War Becomes Crime?, 2001 October 2; 1 (Box 399)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 399U)
  - 3008: NESN Telvision Spots - 9, 2001 October 4; 1 (Box 5)
  - 3940: Tercentennial, 2001 October 4; 1 (Box 586)
  - 3944: Tercentennial Preparations, WVIT, 2001 October 4; 1 (Box 588)
  - 4002: LKL Spot, WTNH, 2001 October 4; 1 (Box 636)
  - 3018: Yale Tercentennial Yale Club Broadcast, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 772)